[{"answer": "Well, she's a wonderful woman who I've gotten to know over the years.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "What was going on there?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "It was a very interesting evening.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Which was it?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I don't see that happening from either of our standpoints actually.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is that something you would ever consider?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, I was a little surprised by that debate, because, all of a sudden, he comes out of nowhere and starts going crazy.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, I'd know if somebody had a picture of me, you know, in that position and wearing those clothes.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "I mean, would you 100 percent recognize yourself in a similar image?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, I was very surprised.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know him at all.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, I'd have to see how he emerges.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "If he emerges, Donald, final, if he emerges as the Republican choice, as their nominee, would that make you more or less tempted to run as an independent?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, that's an excellent question.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What is it about this story that has gripped America, do you think?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, in my mind, based on the evidence that I have heard, and I've still got to hear the rest.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "I mean, given all your experience with these kinds of things, Nancy, do you think there's much doubt that she was responsible for the death of her daughter?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think they could have made a credible defense argument here and that argument would have been that this was an accident, that the child drowned or the child hurt herself, or something happened where it was an accident, and that Casey then sort of lost it.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Does it have any credibility when you do that kind of thing in a courtroom?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, every day, the defense astounds me by what they do.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What do you think the next step's going to be in this case?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Dan, let me ask you, finally -- just running out of time here -- Dan, if you were prosecuting this, based on everything you've seen and heard so far, would you be feeling pretty optimistic of a conviction now?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, tell the truth.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Whether you're Arnold Schwarzenegger, whether you're the guy from IMF, obviously, more serious, whether you're Anthony Weiner -- when you go through something so public and humiliating in so many ways, what's the best way to dust yourself down?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, I love it.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What kind of job is Barack Obama doing as president of your country?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to come back after break and discuss one of those people, Sarah Palin and Donald Trump and a few other of the leading political lights, and get the Jerry Springer verdict.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What kind of people are we to say that's not a good thing?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, I like the man.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What would you make of President Trump as an option for America?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yes, the year we did it in Vietnam.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "You worked with him on Miss Universe, right?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "One, I don't agree with his views.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Why don't you?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, it is so momentary.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "America needs some bravado, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "She connects.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "What do you make of her?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Here's the thing: a candidate is never as popular as he is or she is the moment before they announce.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What do you think of those two candidates?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I'd say right now it would be either Pawlenty or Romney.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Where would your money be on a Republican candidate right now?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Right, not because I was born in the subway, but because I was born in England.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "So technically you can't be president, right?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I watched a very moving interview you did in Britain actually about the whole situation with your family and the Holocaust and the number of relatives that you lost to that.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Where did you get these?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Let me ask you a tricky question, because I've known you a long time and we're good friends and we worked together on \"America's Got Talent.\"", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "And where did I get that hair?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Well, partly tongue in cheek.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I told you, one, I enjoy it.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Why do you keep doing it?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110601pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Snobbery?", "qSentId": 614}]